{
    "id": "4d58adf560934fc2b5c023ea28e9f604",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I met him ......................... a club.",
            "description": "We use at to indicate position at a point.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a1914d39b21f42a4838e14f39e3014b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is some water ......................... the bottle.",
            "description": "We use in to indicate position inside something.",
            "answers": [
                "into",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ca51aadfb4484ec5b571b2abdaeee1e7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The car broke down .......................... the way to work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "to",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a00ea3d4f76a4f1ea3e4bb0bd64068e1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I read an interesting article ........................ the magazine.",
            "description": "We say in a book or a magazine.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "853990f0fc714afb9480ce5148a166c9"
        },
        {
            "question": "She spent the whole day ............................. the bedroom.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3ee968cec1bb407a8ec82d9b3109e347"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you are hungry, there is a banana ............................. the fridge.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "within",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b23935f932e24b948d60e356fd6126ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "They are moving .............................. the suburbs.",
            "description": "We use to to indicate direction.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "beee8903d218453797d23580301bb332"
        },
        {
            "question": "Could you take the children .............................. school?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "473b6ab0ac5f40838e4b9cef7ba45816"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can call me ................................ six.",
            "description": "We use at with clock time.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f0f908956c5d41d09bfe14eef07959ec"
        },
        {
            "question": "The Prime Minister spoke ............................ television last night.",
            "description": "We use on with television.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dc6eae7f7ba140fab660d2189b38020e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you recognize him ............................... this photo?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dc2e74fdc50546058a960e41f7ebbfbe"
        },
        {
            "question": "Bangalore is ............................... the South of India.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ba07b1b075bd4ad983086e3b62272f07"
        }
    ]
}